<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
    <title>Frontend Masters Tutorials</title>
    <link>https://itanyusha.github.io/feeds/frontendmasters-tutorials.xml</link>
    <description>Daily updated feed from https://frontendmasters.com/tutorials/?dg=1&amp;c=tutorials&amp;so=date</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 00:19:42 +0200</lastBuildDate>

	<item>
        <title>How to Use React Compiler for 100% Faster Apps</title>
        <link>https://frontendmasters.com/tutorials/webdevsimplified/react-compiler/</link>
        <description><![CDATA[React 19.2 launched with the React compiler which can drastically increase the performance of your projects. In this video I will show you what the React compiler does, how you can configure it for your exact needs, and most importantly how to avoid potential bugs associated with enabling the compiler.<br><br><img src="https://cdn.frontendmasters.com/assets/tutorials/webdevsimplified/react-compiler/thumb-270.webp" /><br><br>Duration: 19 min<br><br>Authors: Web Dev Simplified]]></description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">ymKYymYvRd</guid>
        <category>Dev Tools</category>
		<category>Performance</category>
		<category>React</category>
		<category>Exclusive</category>
    </item>

	<item>
        <title>Will I Survive These Advanced TypeScript Challenges?</title>
        <link>https://frontendmasters.com/tutorials/webdevsimplified/typescript-challenges/</link>
        <description><![CDATA[Using TypeScript is relatively easy, but writing complex TypeScript types is incredibly difficult. In this video I will be challenging myself with 3 different levels of TypeScript challenge (easy, medium, and hard) to see if I can conquer these ever increasingly difficult TypeScript problems.<br><br><img src="https://cdn.frontendmasters.com/assets/tutorials/webdevsimplified/typescript-challenges/thumb-270.webp" /><br><br>Duration: 29 min<br><br>Authors: Web Dev Simplified]]></description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">EUbvQlpbOC</guid>
        <category>TypeScript</category>
    </item>

	<item>
        <title>I Will Never Use Prettier or ESLint Again</title>
        <link>https://frontendmasters.com/tutorials/webdevsimplified/biome/</link>
        <description><![CDATA[Biome is a tool that aims to replace Prettier, ESLint, and any other formatting/linting tools. It is an all in one tool that does all the linting and formatting for your entire application and best of all it is incredibly easy to setup and use. In this video I will walk you through everything you need to know about Biome to get it set up and configured to your preferences.<br><br><img src="https://cdn.frontendmasters.com/assets/tutorials/webdevsimplified/biome/thumb-270.webp" /><br><br>Duration: 14 min<br><br>Authors: Web Dev Simplified]]></description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">MVwMzWDJna</guid>
        <category>Code Editors</category>
    </item>

	<item>
        <title>2 reasons you should be using single color gradients in CSS</title>
        <link>https://frontendmasters.com/tutorials/kevin-powell/single-color-gradients/</link>
        <description><![CDATA[Learn to create stunning CSS effects using single-color gradients. This tutorial demonstrates practical applications, from enhancing text readability on complex backgrounds to crafting eye-catching gradient borders. Explore techniques for animating gradients and optimizing browser compatibility.<br><br><img src="https://cdn.frontendmasters.com/assets/tutorials/powell/single-color-gradients/thumb-270.webp" /><br><br>Duration: 9 min<br><br>Authors: Kevin Powell]]></description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">RPNByiNKlO</guid>
        <category>Creative Coding</category>
		<category>CSS</category>
    </item>

	<item>
        <title>Spice up user interactions with same-document view transitions</title>
        <link>https://frontendmasters.com/tutorials/kevin-powell/view-transitions-crash-course/</link>
        <description><![CDATA[Dive into same-document view transitions, a great way to easily add some animations to user interactions. In this video, we're looking at the very basics of how they work, and slowly building up to create a few different animations. Along the way, we'll look at common issues that we can run into when using them and how to overcome those issues.<br><br><img src="https://cdn.frontendmasters.com/assets/tutorials/powell/view-transitions-crash-course/thumb-270.webp" /><br><br>Duration: 32 min<br><br>Authors: Kevin Powell]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">GryRwEzTSH</guid>
        <category>Creative Coding</category>
		<category>CSS</category>
		<category>Exclusive</category>
    </item>

	<item>
        <title>Basic React Hooks Crash Course (useState, useEffect, useMemo, useCallback)</title>
        <link>https://frontendmasters.com/tutorials/webdevsimplified/react-hooks/</link>
        <description><![CDATA[Hooks in React are one of the toughest concepts to learn. In this video I will be covering the most popular hooks in React. useState, useEffect, useMemo, useCallback. I will also be showing you all the rules you need to understand about hooks as well as how you can use ESlint to make learning hooks much easier.<br><br><img src="https://cdn.frontendmasters.com/assets/tutorials/webdevsimplified/react-hooks/thumb-270.webp" /><br><br>Duration: 40 min<br><br>Authors: Web Dev Simplified]]></description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">CLkQEJOhyN</guid>
        <category>Next.js</category>
		<category>React</category>
		<category>Exclusive</category>
    </item>

</channel>
</rss>
